[
  {
    "question": "What is true about 5G?",
    "options": [
      "High increased peak bit rate",
      "Lower battery consumption",
      "Larger data volume per unit area",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is not a programming language?",
    "options": [
      "Java",
      "Kotlin",
      "Compiler",
      "Dart"
    ],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Who founded Apple Ink?",
    "options": [
      "Steve Jobs",
      "Sheryl Sandberg",
      "Bill Gates",
      "Sundar Pichai"
    ],
    "answer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is not a peripheral, in computer terms?",
    "options": [
      "Keyboard",
      "Mouse",
      "Motherboard",
      "Monitor"
    ],
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Dart is originally developed by?",
    "options": [
      "Amazon",
      "Google",
      "Apple",
      "Alibaba"
    ],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "A network designed to allow communication within an organization is called:",
    "options": [
      "the Internet",
      "the Intranet",
      "a browser",
      "the World Wide Web"
    ],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Dart is an Object-Oriented language",
    "options": [
      "Yes",
      "No"
    ],
    "answer": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "An ________ is a real-time representation of class",
    "options": [
      "Class",
      "Field",
      "Data Type",
      "Object"
    ],
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "________represent the best practices used by experienced object-oriented software developers.",
    "options": [
      "EB2",
      "Design Patterns",
      "IMS",
      "JCL"
    ],
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "How many time can a Singleton class created?",
    "options": [
      "Only 1 Time",
      "2 Times",
      "3 Times",
      "As Many as Possible"
    ],
    "answer": 0
  }
]